No living creature was harmed
during the filming of this show.
İznik Castle
Episode 71
My bey, drink.
Aygül! Aygül!
Aygül, give it to Cerkutay.
Move out!
I have the antidote!
No one leaves!
Hold the gate!
My bey!
You are well, thank Allah!
I am.
I trusted Kumral Abdal fully.
There, they can only make
hemlock poison.
And this is the cure.
Even a sip...
is enough to heal you.
Don't eat or drink anything
in the Governor's palace.
I'll put a bread on my bag and eat
it if needed, my bey.
If they attempt on some treachery...
we are under your protection.
Sure, my bey.
Drink this.
Drink it!
Take it!
Catch her!
Orhan, don't be afraid.
We are being raided!
Alps! We are being raided!
You all will die today!
You baseborn! Allah creates
and destroys, not you!
Whose dog are you?
Gonca?
Gonca!
Alps! Come, we are being raided!
Mother?
What is it?
I feel a distortion, son.
I wanted to check around.
What is this, mother?
Don't you know?
I'm always like this.
It's a caution.
Let's go together, then.
It'll ease your heart.
A strong girl.
This poison should've killed you.
No! No!
Gonca! No! Gonca!
No!
Gonca! Gonca! Gonca!
Gonca, get up!
Gonca!
Your friend is dead.
Now it's your turn.
Not you, I want the ones holding
your leashes.
Where are the guards?
Mother, these aren't from our tribe.
Protect yourself.
Alps! There is an infiltration!
Come on!
Come on, Julia! Come on!
Mother!
Orhan!
Alps!
We won't survive this.
Gonca!
Gonca, open your eyes!
Kick the door!
Are you alright? Bala?
Mother?
We are alright. Gonca is in a
bad condition.
Gonca!
They infiltrated the tribe for this!
Come on!
She cut the tent and left, my bey!
You won't return before finding her!
-As you order, my bey.
-Come on!
She is bleeding heavily!
Carry her to her tent!
We need to tend her wounds!
I'll find Kumral.
Come on, Master Davud!
Alps!
Come on! Bring it!
Hang on Gonca!
Hang on!
İznik Castle
Your wound seems alright, my bey.
It'll be healed in no time.
We saved our tribe.
This is better than any cure.
I miss Orhan.
Oh, yeah.
So do I.
But her mother Bala...
doesn't see him any different than
her own.
-She looks after him.
-I know.
But know that...
we are exploring for Orhan.
What we see, what we know is
all for Orhan.
These lands that we are in
as guests today...
will be made our home by Orhan.
This is the sacred cause of the Turks.
Malhun, now you are in the future lands
of the Turks.
You said well.
May Allah destine us to see
those days.
Amin.
Brother, I want to return to our
home safely.
I am separated from my loved one.
I miss her.
Brother, you have sister Gonca waiting
for you.
What should I do?
I'm returning to an empty tribe.
Göktuğ, it doesn't fit a man
to be single.
Two kinds of love is good for heart;
love of your country...
and love of a woman.
And...
there is the love of a child, of course.
Add the love of a nephew.
I want to be an uncle, Boran.
Inshallah, brother.
Inshallah.
Göktuğ.
I want to be a father.
Inshallah, brother.
Inshallah.
-Is it ready?
-It is.
Allah is healing.
May I enter, Selcan Hatun?
Come in.
Kumral Abdal, is the arrow poisonous?
The arrow seems to be poisonous.
That's why all alps fell down.
Thank Allah, there is an antidote.
Kumral! Kumral!
Her wound is deep.
We take caution, Allah makes the decision.
Come on, my girl.
Come on.
Mother?
You are also wounded.
I'm alright. What can a small
wound do to me?
Turn to your jobs.
Take Orhan to sleep.
With the name of Allah.
-Is it enough?
-It is.
Mother. Mother, let me check your wound.
-I'm alright, my child.
-We need to fire it.
Harmankaya Castle
That Gregor deceived all the folks
and gave my village to Osman!
Why do you think he'll
work with us?
Because, he is a priest, Nikola.
Before anything, he is a good Christian.
Of course, he'll stand with us against
our eternal enemies.
I don't think so, Kosses.
Where is Priest Gregor now?
With Osman.
Understand it, Nikola!
This is the war between the cross
and the crescent.
Priest Gregor would rather die than
stand with the Turks.
We couldn't get the relic, sir.
As you see, nothing we do works.
We need that priest!
-Summon Samuel.
-Right away.
Believe me, Nikola.
If Priest Gregor stands with us...
with the Flying Fire I have...
I'll create such a gap in Osman's
heart that...
it won't be possible to repair it.
-Sir.
-I want you to go to Priest Gregor.
We need him to destroy Söğüt. And all
lords are waiting for him under the cross.
İznik Castle
You saved my life last night, Osman Bey.
I can't thank you enough.
Your roads are dangerous,
and so is your castle.
Thank Allah...
against all traps...
we have a caution.
For this reason, I'm happy to gain
a friend like you.
Thank you.
Then let's not leave these words
as just words.
If you are so happy to agree
with us...
then pay the coins in advance.
Pay it so that our trade will get
bountiful.
I believe that I'll make more.
Let's have it your way.
Let our trade get bountiful.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
Nothing wrong will happen in İznik.
Both your roads and your goods
are safe with me.
The last verse you learned.
''Humans can't only live with bread...
they live with all the words that
God said.''
Petrus.
Every day, you get closer to be
the saint warrior of the christ.
You are great, kids.
You finished your training.
Now, to become better christians...
Monk Antuan will take you to
St. Beatrice Abby.
It's been eight years since we took them
away from their tribes.
You've done a great job.
You raised Turkmen children
as good Christians.
I'm grateful.
I'm always ready to serve the holy cross.
The christ's love.
When it's fully in their hearts...
we can place the holy cross
anywhere we want.
Don't tell me you returned, empty-handed.
I couldn't take it.
I'm only left with two men.
What is a child, Julia?
A child is a future.
A child is a seed.
A child is a root of a greening tree.
We will take the root before it
greens.
We'll take Osman's dreams.
Tomorrow, this place will be filled
with Turkmen children.
There are children getting education
in Söğüt.
They came from the Kayı Tribe.
They are yours. You will kidnap
them.
And my men will take care of the
children of the other tribes.
I want everything that will hurt them!
This will hurt them well.
You can be sure of that.
Bala, get some rest.
I'll stay here.
I need to be here when Gonca
opens her eyes.
If you don't think for yourself,
think for your baby.
It's your responsibility.
Come on.
What will I say to Boran now?
I hope it's good, Boran.
Something is up.
Let's see, brother.
Bala?
What is this?
Bala, what is this?
Tell me!
Brother, tell me!
Gonca.
Gonca!
-Orhan!
-Where is Orhan?
Tell me!
Orhan is well.
Osman Bey.
We were raided last night.
They infiltrated the tribe to take
the relic.
They couldn't take it.
But we have martyrs.
And Gonca Hatun is severely wounded.
Gonca!
Sister?
Gonca, what did they do to you?
I won't let them get away with this!
Just get up to your feet.
I will make them pay for he
pain they gave you!
I will bury them one by one for
every drop of blood you lost.
Boran.
-You are here.
-I'm here.
I'm here, my rose.
But I'm late.
I couldn't protect you.
I couldn't be your shield.
The sword they swang at you
cuts my heart, Gonca.
Don't. Don't.
Don't, Gonca.
Stay strong.
Don't.
You are here now.
I see you now.
Look at me.
Just get to your feet...
I promise that I will never
leave you again.
You won't spend a day without seeing me.
I swear.
Their faces were masked,
their eyes were devil-like.
They infiltrated the tribe.
One of them, a woman...
we protected ourselves...
but we couldn't protect Gonca.
I couldn't protect my sister, Osman.
She protected Orhan, my baby
and me...
but I couldn't protect her.
Gonca is a strong woman, Bala.
She will be healed.
She will be alright.
Stand tall, Bala.
We've been through many troubles.
Söğüt
Kids, take an apple!
Slowly, slowly!
Slowly!
Which way is Sheik Edebali's lodge?
You look like dervishes,
don't you know where the lodge is?
We aren't from Söğüt but Engörü.
Alright then.
Come with me.
We aren't looking for the lodge
but you.
Come here, little Turks!
This won't kill you.
But it will make you pass out.
Hurry, hide them!
Stop! Who are you?
Let the kids go!
Gonca risked her life to protect us.
Bala, Allah is healing.
We'll take shelter under his name
and wait for the healing.
Don't worry, Gonca will survive.
I was so afraid, Osman.
I was afraid for Orhan.
For our baby.
For losing the relics.
Now I'm tested with my sister's life.
My heart is pounding.
Bala, I'll take their hearts out.
But remove fear from your
pretty eyes.
My bey.
The heathens didn't attack us and the
tribe at the same time for nothing.
It isn't one person's job...
to attack our tribe and us.
It seems that the heathens have united.
It's our job to destroy them all at
where they are united.
But firstly, we need to find the traitor
in the tribe.
I changed the path on our way to İznik.
But very few people knew of this.
Priest Gregor's relic was also a secret.
Do you say it's Gökçe?
Only she was present when we talked
about the relic.
She must've heard it.
In my tent...
she is with Orhan!
If you knew that she would betray,
why didn't you say it, Malhun?
She swore after the carpet
incident, my bey.
She said that it was ignorance,
and we forgave her.
It seems that we were the ignorant ones.
If it's Gökçe who has done
this betreyal.
Don't reveal your suspicion...
before finding out her owner.
This is your job.
Our eyes are on her, my bey.
If you allow me.
Don't worry, my bey.
If you allow me, I want to be with Gonca.
Tell me, Bahadır.
What happened?
They were bloodthirsty, Malhun Hatun.
We protected the tribe.
We beat them, thank Allah.
And where was Gökçe?
I can't say anything, Malhun Hatun.
I couldn't tell who was where
during the fighting.
Now listen to me nicely.
Keep your eyes on Gökçe.
What's wrong, Malhun Hatun? Did Gökçe
do something wrong?
Do as I say, Bahadır.
Keep your eyes on her.
Where she goes, who she talks to;
inform me about everything.
-I brought sherbet, my lady.
-Right here, Gökçe.
Do as I said, Bahadır.
As you command, Malhun Hatun.
Be at ease.
Hurry!
Tie them up!
Give it to the guide leader of the smiths
in Söğüt.
He should use it.
And he should prepare the goods
at once.
-As you order, master.
-Come on now.
My bey, the kids!
They kidnapped the kids from the mosque.
Aytekin! My son!
Ahmet! My Ahmet!
Ahmet!
My son! Bring me my son!
They were already gone when
I woke up, my bey.
The only thing I remember is that
they were led by a woman.
It must be the same woman who
led the attackers here, brother.
My bey, the kids getting schooling
from Dodurga Tribe didn't return.
We are getting the same news from
the other tribes too, my bey.
There were missing children from
near tribes before.
They couldn't be found.
Traitors.
Treacherous dogs.
They tried to fight us first.
But they couldn't beat us.
They weren't strong enough.
Then, they did what fits them,
they plotted.
They set traps.
But they still couldn't
beat us.
Now they are all united and they want
to take our innocent children.
O' people!
Be at ease!
Even the mightiest of the heathen...
is not strong enough to fight
the Turks and their children!
Alps!
Take caution.
Take the most capable tracker alps
with you.
You will attack all the lords' lands
as a wolf attacks a herd of sheep.
As you order, my bey.
But don't return before
finding a track.
If those children of mine
gets hurt...
they won't even be free
after entering their graves.
Go on now!
Go!
I'm not afraid of you.
Kill me if you want.
I could feed the animals with you.
But I have to take you alive.
Tie him.
-Did anyone else run away?
-No, sir.
Let's go.
Come on!
Osman Bey will find us.
Söğüt
Our co-religionists in Söğüt
are loyal to Osman.
It won't be easy to sway them to
a rebellion.
Even though it's difficult, I won't
let Muslims...
pollute our lands any longer,Andreas.
I brought the lords' regards.
The lords are united under the
shadow of the holy cross.
Go on.
They want to make sure that you'll
use your influence to destroy Osman.
Even our most merciless co-religionist
is better than a Turk.
Tell them that I'll do my part.
Be careful.
The first part of this unity is
not getting caught.
God heard our prayers, master.
Soon, Osman.
Christ's children will take
their revenge.
İnegöl Castle
İnegöl Streets
You.
What are you doing here?
This will happen to your
master too!
But not now.
Bilecik Castle
Brother, we can't return before
finding a track.
We must search everywhere.
Who are you? Who are these
children? What are you doing to them?
They are kids from St.Marcus Orphanage.
St.Marcus?
Soldiers, help!
Stop! Stop!
Who do you think is the traitor?
There are many.
I don't know.
But I know one thing.
If I find him...
he'll know the price of
hurting the children.
What did you find, Cerkutay?
It's a child's shoe.
And it's from our tribe.
This way.
It's Bilecik.
-You will pay dearly for this!
-You will!
You will!
Alptekin, get up.
Don't worry, Osman Bey will
save us.
Aren't we Kayı's warriors?
We are!
We must haze these heathens
until Osman Bey comes.
You are right, Ahmet Alp.
But we are out of strenght.
Remember what Kumral Abdal told us.
We have a never-ending power.
We'll evade the heathens off with it.
With the power of faith!
Allahu Akbar!
My spy is back from Söğüt.
Priest Gregor agrees with us
He wants Osman dead.
And even more.
Gentlemen, if Söğüt falls...
so does Osman.
Now, we are on the same ranks
with the priest.
It's a great move, Kosses.
But we need more.
Naturally.
That's why I did more.
Children, the children of the Turks.
I have them.
I'll make them good Christians.
They all will be educated
in the abbey.
When Holy Christ takes his place in
their hearts, we'll have an army.
Great.
Turks trained for killing Turks.
I've never heard a better sentence.
I'm bowing down before you.
Me and the devil.
Guys...
To our little dangerous army.
They set their eyes on the future
of my tent.
I will scratch their eyes out.
They backstabbed my tent.
I will stab this on their back!
If they try to steal our kids...
...who are our roots...
I will hurl my arrows at them!
My Gonca.
She is burning, Kumral Abdal,
do something.
Her wound is deep, my Boran.
We'll pray.
My Gonca will be okay, right?
She will.
Gonca Hatun is strong.
Come up.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim
(With the name of Allah, the merciful, the compassionate)
My Gonca.
My Bala.
You are going to be okay, sister.
You are going to be okay.
She will.
Don't, my Bala.
Don't.
I am the end of the way.
There is no end. The way is eternal, girl.
Do not let my half go away.
You are going to be okay.
Our Ahmet will be here safe and sound.
Our children will grow up together.
I couldn't protect you, my Gonca.
I couldn't.
Give me your blessings.
I do, my Bala.
I do.
You'd do the same...
...if it was you.
Boran.
My Gonca.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come.
We found this on Bilecik way, my Bey.
Our valiants left us a track.
Tell Alps to mount.
We are going to Rogatus.
As you command, my Bey.
Bahadir Alp.
Why did Malhun Hatun stop as soon as
I entered the tent?
What does she hide from me?
Does she suspect me?
Malhun Hatun wanted me to observe you.
She suspects me.
It's because of you.
You caused this.
Oh my stupid head.
I believed you, fell for the gold!
What have I done?
Gokce, don't worry.
I talked to her. I said
"Gokce cares for you...
...she wouldn't harm you."
- So calm down.
- How can I?
Gonca is wounded because of me!
They won't let me live if they figure out!
I didn't know it'd be this much
You tricked me!
Just calm down.
Do not reveal yourself.
I'll handle the rest.
Of course you'll handle the rest.
If something happens to me...
I am not going down alone.
You will as well.
Bilecik Castle.
Why did you invite me, Rogatus?
Lords are now in cooperation, Turgut Bey.
The agreement you signed with Kosses
involves all of us.
It is.
Cut to the chase.
I have a caravan which is about
to enter this land.
It carries belongings of all of
the Lords.
It is your job to protect that caravan
according to our agreement.
Will you be able to protect
no matter who crosses your way?
Our promise is our honor, Rogatus.
Your caravan will be at your castle
in time.
Osman Bey.
Turgut Bey.
What are you doing in Lord's Castle?
I am doing trade for
the welfare of my tent.
Stop!
Rogatus!
Osman Bey, why are you here?
Are you trying to stop our trade
with Turgut Bey becau...
Shut up!
I am here to ask you about the
kidnapped children of Turkmens.
I am here to warn you about what will
happen to the ignobles who...
...raided my tent, murdered my Alps.
Cutting the hand which raises
to us is our tradition.
Blunting the swords which are
pointing us is our tradition!
The castles and the armored soldiers...
nothing can protect you from my wrath!
I will decorate my flags with your heads!
You can't hold me responsible
for everything happening to you.
I don't have any children.
Watch your mouth among my armed soldiers.
How do you think you'll get out of here?
Act now if you can.
Raise your sword if you are brave enough!
Come on!
A Turk has no difference from a wolf.
A Turk is sharper than a sword!
I am Osman Bey,
the son of Ertugrul Ghazi.
Come on!
Act now!
However...
However, you are not brave
enough to kill me.
I will get out of this castle with
taking what I wanted with me.
Just like a wolf getting out of sheepfold.
I am not going to kill you...
Those Turkmen kids who you love so much
will do it, Osman.
When they become a Christian,
they'll face you.
We'll see if you can talk like that
when that time comes.
I wonder if you can.
Boran.
Yes, my rose?
I am here, my Gonca.
Water.
Hold on, my rose.
Come.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(With Allah's name, the merciful, the compassionate.)
My Gonca, you are still burning.
I'll inform Kumral Abdal.
Boran.
Don't leave Boran Alp.
Don't leave Boran.
Don't leave.
The time has come.
However...
I know that...
This is not the end.
No, my Gonca, no.
My Boran...
My rose.
Give me your blessings.
I loved you so much, Boran.
My Gonca.
Don't, please, my other half.
It's not time yet.
We were going to have good days.
Don't leave me early.
Don't leave me, my other half.
Boran.
I am happy to have you, Boran.
Please...
...don't wear yourself down.
My life...
ends here.
My world is you.
What am I to do?
- Bala!
- Daughter.
Bala are you okay?
Don't leave me my Gonca.
Don't.
Gonca.
I'll check on Gonca, mother.
Mother, Gonca is getting worse.
Come.
Gonca!
- Mother.
- My Gonca.
My Gonca! My Gonca!
My Gonca!
"I bear witness that...
...there is no deity but Allah...
...and I bear witness that...
...Muhammad is...
...the messenger of Allah."
My Gonca!
Mother! Mother! Mother!
Gonca sister has gone to the other side.
Boran.
My Bey!
My Gonca has gone
to the other side, my Bey.
May her shahada be blessed, brother.
May her shahada be blessed.
Amin my Bey.
My Bey...
They won't find peace.
They won't.
Of course they won't.
No one who bothers Turks
will live long!
Our sister Gonca...
...has reached the holy position
that we all want.
However...
Do not count martyrs as dead.
Now listen to me carefully.
When we die...
we fall to the ground as a martyr.
But those infidels...
will just be carcases for ravens!
Your tears shall be...
for the longing of our sister Gonca,
who has gone to heaven.
Not for the pain...
...not for the crisis...
...not for...
...especially not for her death.
I am...
I am Osman Bey, the son of Ertugrul Ghazi.
I swear that...
I will not let Gonca and other martyrs!
That ignoble who infiltrated in our tent,
who murdered our alps...
...is the one who kidnapped our children.
We'll find them, brother.
We'll find them.
You'll be the one who takes revenge.
Bilecik Castle.
Ahmet, I am starving, brother.
Hang in there, brother.
We will warm up if we sit close.
Come.
Open it.
What do you want, devil?
We'll have some fun, little mice!
Let go of my brother!
Let go of him!
Let go! Let go!
Let me go!
Let go of my brother!
Let go of me, ignobles!
Where are you taking us?
We are taking you to hell.
Let go!
Let go of us!
Ignobles!
Where are you taking us?
Let go of us, infidels!
Let go!
Stop it, you little mouse!
Let go of us!
Ignobles!
Welcome my beautiful boys.
Don't get away from me.
- Let go of me!
- Don't get away from me.
Let go!
I had a very delicious supper cooked
for you, kids.
You are hungry, right?
Come.
We are
Muslims alhamdulillah(praise be to Allah)
We don't eat pork meat.
What is your name, little man?
My name is Osman Bey.
I am a soldier, you cannot defeat me.
My name is Osman Bey too.
I am a soldier.
My name is Osman Bey too!
You little mice!
We have a long time ahead of us.
I am going to...
...teach you...
...your real names one by one.
Turgut Bey needs to pay for
having a deal with the infidels.
While Turkmen children are kept
captive there...
...it is inappropriate my Bey.
Especially not when you banned
trading with infidels, my Bey.
This is rebellion.
Lords trust Turgut.
They think only Turgut can
protect the caravan.
Let's see if they can protect
their caravan from my wrath.
Goktug, notify Alps.
Notify everyone.
We'll raid Turgut Bey's caravan.
Yes my Bey.
Now you may think that...
...your sun went down...
...that you are all alone in a dark night.
Dark, right?
You are not the only one
who took the pain...
...you are experiencing in
darkness and cold...
The universe is Allah's.
He gave it to us, He is the One to take.
The people are Allah's.
He tests us.
Even the mighty prophet was tested
with this pain.
It was a dark night just like tonight.
First, his uncle Abu Talib.
Then his Khadīja.
The one who believed in him first.
The one who served him.
The one who he leaned on.
Hadrat Khadīja was sick.
Our mighty prophet was crying on her side.
I'd sacrifice myself for his tear!
Our Mother Khadīja...
...heard that Abu Talib deceased.
She tried to relieve our beloved prophet
while she was sick!
My beautifully named, lovely himself,
Mohammed is crying!
He was crying for his uncle!
He was crying for his Khadīja.
He was crying so loudly that
people from outside the room could hear!
Mecca was crying, Medina was crying.
Of course you can cry too, my Boran.
The secret is revealed.
Cry my Boran, cry.
Cry so much that...
...your tears shall put out your
burning heart.
The secret is revealed.
Can a heart bear this separation?
My Gonca has gone to the other side.
The Holy Creator summoned,
how could we tell her not to go?
This is the secret.
Adam is not made only of soil.
He is made of pain too.
Our humanity is assessed
by the pain we can bear.
Cry my Boran, cry.
Cry.
Harmankaya Castle.
Nestor.
You were my right hand.
My confidant..
My most trusted man.
Do not doubt that...
I will make them pay. They crossed
the line when they attacked and killed...
...you in our own land.
I swear.
Samuel!
I want Nestor to be buried
with a knight ceremony!
As you command.
Then you'll go to Sogut.
You'll take the Greek fire to
Priest Gregor.
Sogut...
will burn like hell!
My Gonca...
You are safer there
now that you are martyr.
You migrated, left me with this pain.
I am going to slaughter our enemy...
...with this pain.
For each day you are in grave...
...I will kill one of them.
I'll start with that ignoble first.
I swear that...
...her blood will be the first to shed.
My Bey, take me with you.
Boran.
Go back to the tent.
Lament.
This is my lament, my Bey.
Lamenting before taking my revenge
is haram for me!
Hey Masha Allah!
That's my valiant!
Off we go!
Osman Bey.
You disobey me...
you trade with the ones who hurt me.
Not only you...
I was hurt too.
Consider yourself as a leader, command
all the other Beys...
And if someone doesn't listen,
raid their caravan. Is that it?
It's not only about the caravan...
not only about the trade...
It's about your betrayal.
I do not betray, Osman Bey.
I do what I do for my tent.
Come on now.
Alps!
What is it, Osman Bey?
Why are we meeting here?
- As cautionary.
- Tell me.
- How will we save those kids?
- That's why we are here.
Lords should think you're on their side...
so that we can save kids.
We live in tents. We
can move.
However, this castle is not it.
That's why there is a secret passage.
I know where the secret passage is in the
Bilecik Castle.
It's next to the kitchen.
However, you will open it for us.
I will go into their castle...
to open the passage.
Yes.
We will play a trick on them so that
they will believe you.
Are you okay, my Bey?
I am.
Come on.
I will make you pay for it, Osman Bey.
A valiant like him can stop Osman.
I didn't believe him when Rogatus said
that. We're safe now.
Come on.
We are going to Bilecik.
Won't you eat?
I think you should eat.
You'll be on a diet in Hristos
Monastery anyway.
What Monastery are you
talking about, infidel?
A good Christian monk always eats less.
I'm sure you won't be having a hard time.
Drink.
Drink it!
We all have a holy tree in our
hearts, rising to the sky.
You can't harm that tree whatever you do.
You can't change us.
Don't be so sure, little Turk.
They will be fine even if you
bury the Turks here!
We were born as a Turk, we will
die as a Turk!
You didn't have to come that far.
I wanted to be sure that the
caravan is safe.
Do you think Turgut Bey can
handle it?
Turgut is a powerful and
wise man, Rogatus.
Welcome, Turgut Bey.
Welcome, Turgut Bey. We have been
waiting for you.
I kept my promise.
The caravan is safe.
Turgut Bey.
You're hurt.
Turgut Bey!
- Why are you waiting? Call the doctor!
- Soldiers! Call the doctor!
Carry him to the room.
Turgut Bey.
Slowly.
Osman Bey, bey of Kayı, attacked the
caravan and hurt him.
Turgut Bey protected
our goods with his life.
So, Turgut Bey fought
Osman for us.
You're not as stupid as I think you are.
You side with the powerful ones.
The kids should go to Monastery and
get educated as soon as possible!
Turks are going to end Turks. These
kids should grow up fast.
The kids are going to
the Monastery, Nikola.
They are not going to the order
of Hospitallers. (knights templar)
Firstly, Christianity must
touch their hearts deeply.
And then? All of these kids will become
deathsmen fighting for Christianity.
It's their fate.
However, a good Christian must
hate Turks firstly.
- Söğüt will burn!
- Yes, it will.
Those kids will grow up and then
Osman... Osman...
first Osman and then all of the Turks
in those lands will die.
Osman can't deal with these.
He's destined to die.
Everything's fine for now.
However, we don't know for sure
what will happen at night.
We'll go into the enemy's castle.
It will be so dangerous. Everybody should
take measures.
We will do anything for you, my Bey.
Your way is our way, my Bey.
My Bey, show us a target and we
will attack like a wolfpack.
Mashallah!
A Turk is not scared of dying.
Now, we will take our kids back!
- Come on!
- Your command, my Bey.
- Turgut Bey.
- Mari.
Are you okay? I'm worried.
You don't have to worry.
It's not a severe wound.
What you did is praiseworthy.
You fought for us.
Not for you, I did it to keep my promise.
Your arm is bleeding.
The doctor tightened it.
You must be hurt.
You don't know about
wounds, Byzantine beauty.
Is it okay?
Does it hurt?
- You do it intentionally.
- No. Never.
I owe you a life. I don't ever want
to hurt you.
Where's the Priest?
Is there a problem?
We should be careful.
Is it the Greek fire? (incendiary weapon)
A gift from Lord Kosses to the Priest.
I hope Turgut Bey will succeed.
He's all alone among all those soldiers.
Turgut Bey is a good man.
He's brave.
Of course, he will succeed.
I will kill whoever took my
Gonca away from me.
Of course I will kill that traitor
who hurt me.
When we save the kids, they
will pay for it.
All of them.
The little Turks will go to the
place where they belong, soon.
Look! The devils are coming.
- What will we do, Ahmet Alp?
- My Osman Bey will save us.
Let's gain some time.
Come on.
Kids. How nice! You're all together.
When I see you again, you will have
become good Christians.
You didn't tell me your name but
I have a nice name for you.
From now on, your name is Alex.
Call me whatever you want! A Turk's name
may change but his blood never changes!
Torture us if you want. You will
pay for it.
"My Allah! Have mercy on our great
Muhammad and the Progeny of Muhammad."
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam
"My Allah! Have mercy on our great
Muhammad and the Progeny of Muhammad."
I don't like this, kids. You'll do
what I say.
I am losing my patience!
"My Allah! Have mercy on our great
Muhammad and the Progeny of Muhammad."
The dungeon is that way.
Turgut Bey, stop.
Go back to your place.
Go back to your place so that they think
you're one of them.
May your fight be holy, valiants.
Thank you.
Let me go!
Is everything ready? I don't want any
trouble.
Everything is ready.
Where's Osman, whom you trust so much?
Let me go!
Ahmet.
Monastery.
They are taking the kids to
the Hristos Monastery.
Come on, Alps. They have the kids.
Hurry up.
Okay, my Bey.
I knew I shouldn't have trusted you in the
first place.
I did everything to cure you but
you helped Osman.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com